# Charlotte Mackay

+447875309511 · charlottemackay7@gmail.com · 3 Meadow Vale, Brighton, UK, BN2 7AA https://www.linkedin.com/in/charlotte-mackay/

A motivated recent graduate with a predicted 1st Class Honours Degree in Computer Science for Games. With a wide range of experience that spans over a decade in automotive finance management, coupled with a robust academic foundation in computer science, I bring a unique interdisciplinary perspective to any field.

I am now eager to apply my extensive project management expertise, analytical skills and creative problemsolving abilities to further my experience in a new role.

#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Unreal Engine Game Design Game Programming Visual Studio C++/C# Java JavaScript Web Devlopment Agile Project Management Team leadership Communication Team Work

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Santander Consumer Finance UK

Aug 2021 - Present

#### **Technical Admin Advisor**

Ensure excellent customer outcomes by maintaining high service levels, demonstrating skills in customer engagement and satisfaction.

#### Accomplishments:

- Deliver outstanding customer service and build a strong rapport with customers.
- Efficiently managed complex administrative tasks, showcasing attention to detail and precision.
- Handle sensitive customer data in compliance with legislation.
- Process Data Subject Access Requests (DSARs) in line with GDPR, further highlighting a high level of understanding and working knowledge of data protection.
- · Consistently over-achieve productivity and quality targets.
- Collaborate with other teams throughout the business to improve the customer journey.

#### PSA Finance April 2019 - Aug 2021

#### Training and Projects Manager

Lead the training and development of the customer services team, alongside delivering key business-defining projects.

#### Accomplishments:

- Led digital projects, conducting performance analyses post-delivery
- Undertook QA testing and implementation of critical business systems, including telephony and CRM systems, reflecting skills in quality assurance processes.
- Contributed to developing and delivering a new customer management system, showcasing ability in learning and implementing complex systems.
- Developed and executed a new onboarding training structure, leading to improved staff retention and performance.
- Reviewed and improved departmental processes, demonstrating a skill for optimising operational
  efficiency.
- Managed multiple projects and staff training.

PSA Finance April 2017 - April 2019

#### **Customer Services Call Centre Manager**

Responsible for leading the team in achieving high service levels in a busy and changing call centre environment. Reflecting leadership and team management skills.

#### Accomplishments:

- Managed recruitment, training, and coaching of the team.
- Analysed call centre data for process improvements, driving efficiency and customer satisfaction.
- Designed and managed staff incentives and performance, fostering an engaging work environment.

#### **Santander Consumer Finance UK**

Jan 2011 - April 2017

#### Various admin and leadership roles

Throughout my career at SCUK, I have held various roles, always keen to learn as much as I could and improve my skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

## The University of Brighton BSc (Hons) Computer Science for Games

Sept 2021 - June 2024

Created a Procedural Generation engine for unique and replayable game worlds for the final year dissertation project using Unreal Engine 5, utilising project management, programming and development skills.

#### Key Modules and grades:

- · Dissertation Project: A
- Programming Languages: A+
- · Game Design and Development: A
- Games Programming: A
- Programming Languages: A+
- Game Development Frameworks: A+
- Web-Based Game Development: A
- Game Engine Fundamentals: B
- · Artificial Intelligence for Games: B

The Open University Jan 2016 - May 2018

Diploma of Higher Education in Business Management

#### **PRINCE2 Project Management**

December 2014

**AXELOS Global Foundation and Practitioner** 

#### **Chartered Institute of Management**

June 2013

Level 3 Certificate in First line Management

#### St. Wilfrid's School & Sixth Form

Sept 2003 - May 2010

3 A-levels at B-C grade in Biology, Psychology andSociology. 1 AS level in Philosophy with ethics.12 GCSEs including math, English, and science at B-C grade.